opinionstage.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Opinion Stage

## 1\. General

We recognize that your privacy is very important, and we take it seriously. This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures governing the collection and processing (i.e., access, use, disclosure, and transfer) of your personal data when you use the website https://www.opinionstage.com and any related software (collectively, the “Website”). The Website provides services and templates for creation and maintenance of polls, surveys, quizzes, slideshows, lists, stories and forms (the “Services”). We will not collect and process your personal data in any manner that is incompatible with this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Your consent

By using the Website and the Services, you consent to our processing of your personal data for the specified, explicit, and legitimate purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

We will seek your express consent prior to: (1) using your personal data for any purposes that are not explicitly indicated in this Privacy Policy; (2) providing you with any marketing communication; (3) transferring your personal data to third parties that are not indicated in this Privacy Policy; or (4) significantly amending this Privacy Policy.

## 3\. Responsible authority

The authority responsible for the collection and processing of your personal data is Opinion Stage Ltd., having a principal place of business at Zmora 8, Shoham, 6085000, Israel.  
Phone: +1-347-708-0047  
E-mail: [info@opinionstage.com](mailto:info@opinionstage.com)

## 4\. Types of personal data we collect

Throughout this Privacy Policy, the term “personal data” refers to all information that allows us to identify you as a natural person. We collect the following types of personal data:

 **Registration data.** When you register your user account on the Website, we collect the following personal data:

  * Your username;
  * Your password;
  * Your email address;
  * Your website address;
  * Your social media account information (Facebook/Twitter/Google+) (optional).

 **Billing data.** When you upgrade your user account through the Website, we collect your billing information:

  * If you decide to pay for the upgrade of your user account by using your credit card, we collect your credit card information, first name, last name, and email address; or
  * If you decide to pay for the upgrade of your user account by using your PayPal account, we collect your PayPal information.

 **Contact data.** If you contact us by email or any other available means, we will collect your email address and other available contact details, the content of your email messages, and our responses.

 **Log files.** The log files collected by us may include some of your personal data, such as your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and non-personal data, such as your web request, browser type, referring/exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, landing pages, and pages viewed. Log files are automatically reported by your browser each time you access the Website. When you use the Website, our servers will automatically record the information that your web browser sends.

 **Content data.** In some cases, persons may be asked to provide certain personal data through the polls, surveys, quizzes, slideshows, lists, stories and forms created through the Website (the “Content Data”). Please note that we do not make decisions about what personal data is requested as the Content Data or for what purposes such Content Data is used. The user that uses the Services and requests the Content Data is the person who is responsible for handling the Content Data. We merely store and process such personal data on our servers for the purpose of provision of the Services.

## 5\. Purposes of personal data collection and processing

The personal data we collect from you will be used only for providing you with the requested Services, performing the contract with you, and pursuing our legitimate interests. Such purposes substitute a legal basis for collection and processing of your personal data.

 **Registration data.** We will use your personal data for creating and maintaining your user account on the Website and providing you with the Services. We may also use your registration data to send you educational information and important notices related to the Services.

 **Billing data.** If you upgrade your user account, we will use your billing data to charge you the recurring monthly fees for the Services.

 **Content data.** If you submit any personal data as a part of the content data, we will use such personal data for providing you with the requested Services only. Please note that, if you decide to publish a product generated as a result of the provided Services (e.g., a poll, a quiz, or a form) online, some of such content data may become public. Please keep in mind that it is your sole responsibility to decide which content data will become publicly available. We ask you to take reasonable security measures and limit the exposure of content data.

 **Contact data.** We will use your contact data to respond to your questions, messages, and requests.

 **Log Files.** We will use the log files to efficiently provide you with the Services, optimize and analyze the Services, detect and resolve malfunctions of the Services, and other purposes that fall within the scope of our legitimate interests, such as:

  * To analyze how the Services are used;
  * To diagnose technical problems of the Services;
  * To maintain security of the Services;
  * To personalize the content of the Services;
  * To remember information and help you to efficiently access your user account;
  * To monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; and
  * To track the content generated by the users as a result of the provision of the Services, as necessary to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other applicable laws.

If we would like to use your personal data for any purposes that are not mentioned in this Privacy Policy, we will seek your explicit consent in advance for that particular purpose.

## 6\. Marketing communication

If you provide us with your prior explicit consent, we will use your contact information to send you marketing messages (e.g., advertisement, brochures, and updates on our new products and Services). If you do not want to receive such messages, at any time, you may opt out by following the instructions in the message (e.g., by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link) or by contacting us directly at [info@opinionstage.com](mailto:info@opinionstage.com)

Please note that we may send you information about our new Services that are closely related to the Services already used by you without obtaining your prior consent.

## 7\. Disclosure of personal data to third parties

If it is necessary to ensure the provision of the Services, proper functioning of the Website, and performance of a contract concluded with you, we may share your personal data with third parties that provide us with technical support or provide services on behalf of us.

If we do this, we will put reasonable efforts to ensure that such third parties guarantee an adequate level of protection of your personal data that is compatible with this Privacy Policy. Please note that some of the third parties indicated in this Privacy policy may be located outside of the jurisdiction in which you reside.

The third parties that may have access to your personal data are specified below.

  *  **Cloud storage and hosting providers.** Our servers are located in secure AWS Amazon servers located in the U.S. AWS Amazon privacy policy is available at <https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq>
  * **Communication providers.** To better facilitate communications with us and to provide you with the best possible customer service, we use a chat and support center developed and provided by Intercom Inc. located in the U.S. The responsible authority in the event of data collection during the use of the chat application is Intercom Inc. The Privacy Policy of Intercom Inc. is available at <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies> privacy
  *  **Billing providers.** For the billing of the Services, we use the following third-party payment processors:
    *  **BlueSnap Inc.** located in the U.S. The Privacy Policy of BlueSnap Inc. is available at <https://home.bluesnap.com/privacy-policy>.
    *  **PayPal** located in the U.S. The Privacy Policy of PayPal is available at <https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>.
    *  **ChargeBee** located in India. The Privacy Policy of ChargeBee is available at <https://www.chargebee.com/privacy/>.

 **Non-personal data.** We may share your non-personal data, such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, and a number of clicks, with interested third parties to help them to understand the usage patterns for the Services.

 **Transfer of personal data outside the EEA.** If you are a resident of the EEA, some of your personal data may be transferred outside the EEA. In case it is necessary to make such a transfer of your personal data, we will ensure that the jurisdiction in which the recipient third party is located ensures an adequate level of protection of your personal data or we conclude an agreement with the respective third party that ensures such protection.

## 8\.  Duration of storage and deletion of your personal data

We will store you personal data as long as it is necessary for providing you with the requested Services, until the personal data is required for the legitimate purpose of its collection, or until you stop using the Services. If your personal data is no longer necessary for any of such purposes, we will immediately delete such personal data from our systems.

Please note that user accounts on the Website do not expire. You can use the Services continuously, if you comply with the Terms of Use. When we receive a complete account deletion request from you, we will delete the personal data from all our systems immediately, unless, under the applicable law, retention obligations apply.

## 9\. Your rights

You can exercise your rights regarding your personal data collected through the Website by contacting us by email at [info@opinionstage.com](mailto:info@opinionstage.com).

 **The right to access, rectification, portability, and erasure.** Upon our request, we will provide you with information on if and what personal data is stored by us. In order to fulfill this request, you will need you to provide us with an identifying piece of data so we can locate the personal data on our system. You will then have the right to request us to access the personal data, rectify/change it, transfer it to you, or request us to erase it from our systems.

 **The right to object and restrict processing.** You have the right to object or restrict processing of your personal data, such as request us to stop sending emails to you. Please note that, in this case, we may not be able to provide you with certain services.

 **The right of withdraw consent.** If you provide us with your express consent, you can revoke it from us at any time.

 **The right to launch a complaint.** If you would like to launch a complaint about the way in which your personal data is handled, please contact us first. After you contact us, we will send you a confirmation that we have received your complaint. Afterwards, we will investigate your complaint and provide you with our response within a reasonable timeframe but no later than 2 weeks. If you are a resident of the European Union and you are not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint, you have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority.

## 10\. Children's privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to us. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal data from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register on the Website. If we become aware that we have collected personal data from a person under the age of 18 without verification of parental consent, we will immediately remove such personal data. The parent or guardian of a person under the age of 18 who has provided us with personal data without obtaining parental or guardian consent in advance may contact us and request us to destroy or de-identify the personal data.

## 11\. How we protect personal data

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards (e.g., limited access to personal data and secured networks) to preserve the integrity and security of your personal data. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any personal data you share with us or guarantee that your personal data may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach that occurs outside of our reasonable control. In the event that personal data is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take the necessary steps to mitigate the breach as required by the applicable law.

## 12\. Links to other websites

This Privacy Policy applies to the Website only. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Website, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on the Website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies.

## 13\. Cookies

 **What are cookies?**

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are sent to your browser and stored on your computer, mobile phone or other device when you visit a website. The cookies send information back to the originating website or another website that recognizes that cookie. Cookies can be permanent (these are known as persistent cookies) where they remain on your computer until you delete them, or temporary (these are known as session cookies) where they last only until you close your browser. Cookies can also be first-party cookies which are set by the website which is being visited, or third-party cookies which are set by a website other than the one being visited.

 **What cookies do we use?**

 **Service functionality cookies.** We use these cookies for providing the full functionality of the Services, such as a “login & registration” cookie that saves your login credentials in protected areas to save the need to login to the Website on each visit, and a “block repeat voting” cookie that saves your vote in the cookie to block multiple voting. These cookies are first-party cookies, and can be either permanent or temporary. Without these cookies the Website and the Services won't work properly or won't be able to provide certain features and functionalities.

 **Advertising cookies.** These cookies can be used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help manage the delivery of advertising campaigns. Advertising cookies are also used to customize the advertising across the Website and make it more relevant to you. Advertising cookies are placed by third parties such as advertisers, ad platforms and their agents, and can be permanent or temporary cookies. In short, they are related to advertising services provided by third parties on the Website.

 **Third-party cookies.** On some pages of the Website, we may have content from third-party services, such as YouTube or Facebook. Please note that we do not control any cookies which are used by these services and you should check the relevant third-party website for more information about these.

 **How to manage & remove cookies?**

If you would like to restrict, block or remove cookies, you can do this through your web browser settings. The “Help” function within your web browser will tell you what you need to do. You can also visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for more information on how to manage and remove cookies across a number of different Internet browsers. Please note that disabling cookies may prevent you from accessing some of the Services and enjoying the full features of the Website.

## 14\. Google Analytics

The Website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics is used to analyze how the Services are used, diagnose service or technical problems and monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns. Google Analytics also uses cookies and the information generated by the cookie regarding your use of the Website (including your IP address) is transmitted to a Google server in the U.S. and stored. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Website, compiling reports on Website activity, and providing other services relating to Website activity and Internet usage. Google may also pass this information on to third parties in so far as this is required by law or if third parties process the data on Google’s behalf. Google will not under any circumstances associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

You can prevent these cookies being stored by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, we wish to point out that doing so may mean you will not be able to enjoy the full functionality of the Website. You can also prevent the data generated by cookies about your use of the Website (including your IP address) being passed to Google and the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin available under the following link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de>.

By using the Website you agree to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described above and for the aforementioned purpose. You can find more detailed information on Google’s [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

## 15\. Third party advertisements

We may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. We do not provide any personal data to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information. We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit the Website. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personal data (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to the Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and Networking Advertising Initiative at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>.

## 16\. Amendment of the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the amended version on the Website. Your continued use of the Website after posting such an amended version will constitute your acknowledgment of the amendments and your consent to abide and be bound by the amended Privacy Policy. Please regularly review this Privacy Policy in order to be aware of new amendments. For significant changes in the Privacy Policy, or where required by the applicable law, we may seek your explicit consent to the changes stated in the Privacy Policy.

## 17\. Contact Information

If you have any questions about our practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@opinionstage.com](mailto:info@opinionstage.com) and specify the keyword “Privacy” in the subject line.

Our other contact details are:

 **Address:** Opinion Stage Ltd., Zmora 8, Shoham, 6085000, Israel  
 **Phone:** +1-347-708-0047

## 18\. Last amendment

This Privacy Policy has been last amended on 2nd of May 2018.
